去伯班克机场  谢谢
Burbank Airport, please.
拉斯维加斯  我们来啦
Vegas, here we come!
不带老公
No husbands,
不带男友  不设下限
no boyfriends, no rules.
不设下限吗
No rules?
我们不会喝醉酒后  去跟蓝人乐团
We're not gonna get drunk and have a six-way
蓝人乐团  知名三人打击乐团  成员会把全身涂成蓝色
大搞床上"六人行"的吧
with the Blue Man Group, are we?
不会
No.
那就还是有下限啊
So there are some rules.
行
Fine.
不带男友  不带老公  设了下限
No husbands, no boyfriends, some rules.
谢谢更正
Thank you.
赌城
Vegas!
女人不在  男人爽快
The ladies are away, the boys will play.
欢乐无极限
Anything can happen.
大家一起疯
It's gonna get crazy.
龙与地下城
Dungeons & Dragons!
我买了一套新比基尼
I got a brand-new bikini,
泳池畔的免费酒水就靠这对胸器了
so drinks at the pool are on these.
我有一件性感上衣写着"来嘛  帅哥"
I got a sexy new tube top that says "Come hither"
以及一瓶名为"滚开  色鬼"的防狼喷雾
and a can of pepper spray that says "Close enough, Jack."
我准备了一些旧的内衣要丢到
I got some old underwear I'm gonna throw on stage
加斯·布鲁克斯的演唱会舞台上
at the Garth Brooks concert.
美国知名乡村歌手  唱片曾创下乡村音乐最高纪录
等等  为啥要丢旧的
I'm sorry, why old?
因为我上次见他的时候  丢了新的
'Cause last time I saw him, I threw new ones
结果也啥都没捞着
and it got me nothing.
我有一组全新内含七个的
I've got a brand-new seven piece set
多面骰
of polyhedral dice.
新骰子味道真棒
Hello, new dice smell.
我有"天神之力头盔"  "速度之靴"
I've got my helm of lordly might, my boots of speed,
如果玩得太嗨
and if things get too exciting,
我还带了"哮喘者的吸入之器"
my inhaler of asthma.
我有个全新嗜血野蛮战士
I got my new bloodthirsty savage warrior
他会蹂躏所有出现在他面前的人
who will lay waste to all who stand before him.
我还明智地午餐只吃了色拉
And I had a sensible salad for lunch,
所以现在想吃多少披萨都行
so I can eat all the pizza I want.
拜托  我们是要坐在这
Come on, are we gonna sit around chatting
像少女一样聊天叽叽喳喳呢
like a bunch of teenage girls,
还是要当永远没机会跟少女发生关系
or are we gonna play D & D like a bunch of teenage boys
只能玩龙与地下城的寂寞少男啊
who are never gonna have sex with those teenage girls?!
赌城  赌城  赌城
Vegas! Vegas! Vegas!
莫夫斯克海克地下城
The Dungeon of Mofooskay-Heeko!
生活大爆炸 第六季  第二十三集
我很庆幸今晚露西要工作
I'm actually glad Lucy had to work tonight.
让我不用尴尬地跟她说
Saved me the awkward conversation about
我今晚没空  要跟兄弟们玩
how I was gonna be hanging with my bros.
你们俩有任何对话是不尴尬的吗
Isn't every conversation you two have awkward?
好惨  确实没有
Painfully so.
我们有个小规矩  如果通话时没人说话
We have this rule on the phone that if no one talks
超过三分钟  就可以直接挂掉
for three minutes, you can just hang up.
好中意她啊
So into her.
你们好就能开始了
Ready whenever you guys are.
行  我们马上来
Yeah, yeah, we'll be right there.
-莱纳德  -怎么了
- Yeah, Leonard... - Yeah?
我对于霍华德
I'm not sure how I feel
代替你当地下城主有点不是滋味
about Howard being dungeon master instead of you.
真有义气
Oh, that's nice.
但别紧张嘛  偶尔换换也不错
But relax, sometimes change is good.
你以前也担心扎克瑞·昆图
Uh, you were worried about Zachary Quinto
扎克瑞·昆图  知名演员  曾出演过《英雄》
后出演新一代星际迷航里的斯波克角色
来演斯波克会不好  可后来你也喜欢他了
being the new Spock, but you wound up liking him.
拜托
Oh, please.
每次提到改变的话题
Every time the topic of change comes up,
你都用扎克瑞·昆图来堵我的嘴
you throw Zachary Quinto in my face.
我不满邮差换了新发型
I'm upset the mailman has a new haircut:
扎克瑞·昆图
Zachary Quinto.
我不高兴开始夏令时开始
I'm upset that daylight saving time started:
扎克瑞·昆图
Zachary Quinto.
我不爽夏令时结束  扎克瑞·昆图
I'm upset daylight saving time ended: Zachary Quinto.
我最后再说一次
I'm saying this for the last time
扎克瑞·昆图是一个奇特
Zachary Quinto was a weird,
美好  又出乎意料的特例
wonderful, unrepeatable event.
所以少拿他来说事
So stop using him against me.
好啦  开始吧
Okay, here we go.
你们发现自己身在一个
You find yourselves in
巨木参天的原始森林里
an overgrown old forest.
在你们面前  有一棵巨型橡树
Before you is a giant oak tree
树上有张脸
with a face on it
看起来很像是尼克拉斯·凯奇哦
that looks a lot like Nicolas Cage.
他说"请小心上路
He says, "travel with caution.
这片森林是许多陨落于此的
These woods are home to the bones
各路英雄的
of many a fallen...
埋骨之地"[模仿凯奇声音]
hero!"
你看  霍华德跟我一样好嘛
See, Howard's just as good a dungeon master as I am.
什么一样好
As good?
你跟他比差远了  四眼田鸡
You just got pantsed in the schoolyard, four-eyes.
别吵啦  集中注意力
Hey, come on, guys, focus.
伟大的尼克拉斯·凯奇树
Oh, mighty Nicolas Cage tree,
我们由衷感谢您的提醒
we thank you for your warning,
但我们都是英勇的战士
but we are brave warriors,
任何危难或死亡也阻挡不了我们的决心
and nothing short of death will keep us from our goal.
露西又有空了
Oh, Lucy's free after all.
再见
See ya.
你不能说走就走啊
Hey, hey, hey, you can't leave.
才刚开始玩呢
We just started.
你说得对  我应该玩完才是
You're right, I should finish the game.
我举起我的强化长剑
I take my plus-one long sword,
朝自己脸上一桶
stab myself in the face with it.
我死了  我要去跟姑娘约会啦
I'm dead, I've got a date with a girl.
再见
Bye.
没事的  你们看
We'll be fine, watch.
突然  从满是血的
Suddenly, a spectral shape
库萨帕里尸体上  有东西缓缓升起
rises from Koothrappali's bloody corpse,
并说道"别担心  兄弟们
and says, "don't worry, buddies,
拉杰之魂将会
ghost Raj will help
带领你们走过这片森林
guide you through the forest."
"我只是棵树  但如果我是你
"Well, I'm just a tree, but if I were you,
我会听你死鬼朋友的话"
I'd listen to your ghost friend!"
快  对他俯首称臣吧
Go on, give him your lunch money.
我很开心你今晚有空出来玩
I'm very happy you were able to hang out tonight.
我也是
Me, too.
并不是说你是来让我开心的
Not that it's up to you to make me happy.
但如果你觉得求关爱的人很性感
Uh, well, unless you find neediness sexy.
这样的话  你将要和
In which case, you're about to have dinner
地球上最性感的男人吃饭了
with the hottest man on the planet.
我可以告诉你件事吗
Can I tell you something?
跟你见面让我非常紧张
I was so nervous about seeing you,
所以在离开公寓前
before I left my apartment,
我把整管止汗剂抹遍全身
I put roll-on antiperspirant all over my body.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
如果汗从我脑袋顶上喷出来
If sweat starts squirting out the top of my head,
你就知道原因了
you'll know why.
很抱歉让你遭这种罪
I, uh, I'm sorry to put you through that.
没关系啦
Oh, it's okay.
我一直在逼自己
I've been trying to force myself
做一些让我害怕的事情
to do things that make me scared.
比如说还有什么是你想做的
What else have you been thinking about doing?
我想想
Well, let's see.
我很想告诉帮我剪头发的女士
I'd love to be able to tell the lady who cuts my hair
我不喜欢留刘海
that I don't like bangs.
我喜欢你的刘海
I like your bangs.
谢谢  我也很喜欢
Oh, thanks, I like 'em, too.
还有什么
What else?
似乎这俩难度一样
It's kind of a tie between
在餐馆把菜退回去
sending food back in a restaurant
和拒绝挨家按户兜售杂志的小孩
and saying no to those kids who sell magazines door-to-door.
是啊  这俩都难以启齿
Mm, yeah. Those are both toughies.
就是啊
I know.
我订阅了两年的《枪支与弹药》杂志
I have a two-year subscription to Guns & Ammo.
我用肩膀用力去顶那扇密门
I push my shoulder against the secret door
看看能不能推开它
to see if it gives way.
能
It does.
他还会配音效呢
He does sound effects, too!
我也一直有配音效呀
Hey, I always did sound effects.
一大群嗜血蝙蝠飞过地下城
A-A swarm of bloodthirsty bats fly through the dungeon.
它们袭击附近的独角兽
Uh, uh, they attack a nearby unicorn.
好吧  我也来给你的音效配个音效吧
Okay, well, I have a sound effect for those sound effects.
猜猜谁回来了
Guess who!
你们怎么回来了
What are you doing back?
问得真好  艾米你说吧
That's an excellent question. Amy?
这个嘛
Uh, well...
在我们过安检的时候
when we were going through security,
我从队伍里被拉出来搜身
I got pulled out of line for a pat-down.
那个
The, uh,
运输安全局的人有点毛手毛脚
TSA agent got a little handsy...
我貌似就用手肘撞断了她的鼻骨
I may have broken her nose with my elbow.
长话短说  她上了禁飞名单
Long story short, she's on the No Fly List
回来时  还可能有一架无人飞机跟着我们
and we might have been followed here by a drone.
对不起嘛
I'm sorry.
我感觉自己就像个白痴
I feel like such an idiot.
没那么糟啦
Oh, it's not so bad.
损失金钱  内心充满耻辱
You lost money, you're filled with shame
还被陌生人摸来摸去
and you got groped by a stranger.
赌城就像这样  你成功了
I mean, that's Vegas, you nailed it.
祝你们今晚过得愉快
You guys enjoy your evening.
我先走了  省得又搞砸其他人的周末
I'm gonna go before I ruin anybody else's weekend.
这样才乖嘛
That's my girl.
不  艾米  别走
No, no. Amy, wait.
我知道今晚没能如你们所愿
Uh, uh, I know it's not the night you had in mind,
但你们何不留下来  跟我们一起玩呢
but why don't you guys stay and play with us?
-会很好玩哦  -会好玩吗
- It'll be fun. - It would-- fun?
好吧  三周前
Yeah, okay, three weeks ago,
你买了一罐颗粒型花生酱
you bought crunchy peanut butter,
而现在你又让这帮女人跟我们一起玩
but now you want the girls to play D & D--
你是不是吸毒吸傻了
do you have a drug problem?
这有什么关系
What's the big deal?
拉杰开溜了  我们可以找人替他呀
Raj bailed, so we could use some extra players.
我只是从来没跟女人一起玩过龙与地下城
Well, I've just never played Dungeons & Dragons with girls before.
别害怕  小宝贝
Oh, don't worry, sweetie.
没人跟女人玩过这个
No one has.
你觉得怎么样
So, what do you say?
我把决定权留给地下城主
I'll leave it up to the dungeon master.
好的  一朵长得
Yeah, a... satanic fungus
特别像阿尔·帕西诺[演员]的恶魔菌类
that looks suspiciously like Al Pacino
从森林植被冒出来说
rises from the forest floor and says,
"你来玩龙与地下城
"You're playing D & D.
你也来玩
You're playing D & D.
所有人都来一起玩
This whole apartment...
龙与地下城"
...is playing D & D."
谁想来一杯
Okay, who wants a drink?
佩妮  我们玩游戏的时候
Yeah, we-- now, Penny, we don't consume alcohol
不能喝酒
during Dungeons & Dragons.
那会影响我们的判断力
It impairs our judgment.
这不是酒
Oh, this isn't alcohol.
这是能让我喜欢你的魔力药水
It's a magic potion that makes me like you.
麻烦给我来双份
Double potion, please.
游戏开始
Okay, here we go.
你们发现
You find yourselves
迎面走来两个笨重的食人魔
face-to-face with two hulking ogres.
"你们来地下城干什么
"What are you doing in our dungeon?
纳命来"
You shall die!"
我真起鸡皮疙瘩了  看
Okay, literal goose bumps. Look.
你们会怎么做
What do you do?
我会拔出我的剑
I draw my broadsword.
我举好我的魔棒
I ready my quarter-staff.
我会喝我的药水
I drink my potion.
-我说"冲上去揍大的"  -算了
- I say we attack the big one. - You know what?
把骰子给我  我想掷骰子
Give me the dice, I want to roll.
这事应该由地下城主来做
Well, the dungeon master's supposed to roll.
我们还应该在维加斯
Yeah, well I'm supposed to be in Vegas
吃海鲜自助餐吃到吐的  快给我
throwing up on a shrimp buffet. Now give it.
我得掷多少点
All right, what do I need?
15或大于15
Uh, 15 or higher.
目标15点  就要15点以上
15's the point, the point is 15.
给老娘让点儿地方  准备上啦
Give the little lady some room, here it is, coming out.
Sixteen!
真棒
Yes!
快告诉我咱们是玩钱的
Oh, please tell me we're playing for money.
这可比赢钱还好
Oh, even better than money.
你赢得了经验值
You gained experience points.
-麻烦再来点药水  -好
- More potion, please. - Yeah.
你的蟹饼怎么样
How are your crab cakes?
有点臭
Kind of funky.
-很不错啊  -是吗
- That's great. - It is?
"臭"在印度是另一个意思吗
Does "funky" mean something different in India?
不不
No, no.
你不是一直想在餐馆里把菜退回去吗
Uh, you've always wanted to send your food back in a restaurant;
这下机会来了
here's your chance.
没关系  我不吃就是了
It's okay. I just won't eat 'em.
别傻了  服务员
Don't be ridiculous. Waiter?
菜还行吗
Everything all right?
是的
Uh... yeah.
你过得还行吗
Everything all right with you?
是的
Yes.
好的  谢谢  再见
'Kay, thanks, bye.
等一下
Hold on.
你不是有别的事要告诉他吗
Isn't there something else you wanted to tell him?
不  没关系的
N-No, it-it's fine. Uh...
他不是美国人  不理解咱们
He's from a different country; he doesn't understand our ways.
别犯傻了  快告诉他吧
Don't be silly. Just tell him.
我得去趟卫生间
I have to go to the bathroom.
绝对不是因为蟹饼有点臭
And it's not because the crab cakes are funky.
那您没问题吧
So you're okay here?
是的  抱歉
Uh, yeah, sorry.
她只是太害羞了
She's just a little shy.
我们第一次见面的时候  她因为太过紧张
The-the first time we met, she was so nervous,
为了躲我  甚至从卫生间爬窗逃跑呢
she climbed out a bathroom window to get away from me.
糟糕
Uh-oh.
拉杰
Hey, Raj.
说来也好笑
Funny story.
加油  老娘要整死几个食人魔
Come on, mama wants a pair of dead ogres!
17  大个儿的食人魔死了
17! The larger ogre is dead!
另一个食人魔说
The-the other ogre says,
"你杀了我哥哥
"You killed my brother.
食人魔感恩节被毁了"
Now ogre Thanksgiving is ruined."
真是太生动了
That is amazing.
他甚至让我关心起食人魔来了
He made me care about the ogre!
艾米  还剩一个食人魔
All right, Amy, there's one ogre left.
-灭了他  -好的
- Take him out! - Okay.
就当是运输安全局的那群人
Pretend he's that TSA agent. Come on.
Nineteen!
太好了
Yes!
没想到这里比去赌城还好玩
This is turning out to be even better than Vegas!
才没有呢
No, it's not!
露西
Lucy?
好久不见
Long time no see.
你不太了解我
You don't know me very well,
每次你从卫生间窗户爬出去
but each time you crawl out a bathroom window
躲避我  我的男子气概都流失许多
to escape my company, it chips away at my masculinity.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你为什么非要这样离开
Why would you leave like that?
是你逼我的
You were pushing me;
我很明显不想把菜退回去
I clearly didn't want to send my food back,
但你还是逼我这么做
and you tried to make me do it anyway.
好吧  如果我让你不高兴了
Okay, if I upset you,
你何不直接对我说呢
then why didn't you just say something?
我怎么能对你直说呢  我甚至不能跟那个
Well, how can I tell you I'm upset if I can't tell the woman
理发店的女人说我的额头是个人亮点来着
at Supercuts that my forehead's my best feature?
这让我很害怕
It's scary.
我很喜欢你
Yeah, well, I like you a lot,
这也很让我害怕
and that's scary for me.
主要是因为你会随时逃走
Mostly because you're a proven flight risk.
你怎么会特别喜欢我呢
How could you like me a lot?
其中一个是因为
Well, uh, for one thing,
你的感情问题比我还严重
you have bigger emotional problems than I do,
我觉得这种女孩子特别迷人
and I find that very attractive in a woman!
我也不知道
I-I don't know. I just...
我觉得你特别好
I think you're wonderful.
我的汗都从头顶喷出来了
I'm sweating out of my head.
巨龙从天上坠落
The dragon falls from the sky,
一头栽进了火山岩浆
crashing into the volcano!
等一下
But wait!
他还没死
He's not dead.
他缓缓爬了出来
He crawls out,
伸展了一下自己的翅膀  准备攻击
spreads his wings and prepares to attack.
等等
Yeah, uh, wait!
他有没有先说点什么呢
Doesn't he say something first?
比如用我们喜欢的名人的声音来说
You know, maybe in the voice of a beloved celebrity?
好吧
Fine.
"瞧  都这么多年了
"You'd think, after all these years,
我明明应该知道别在火山上乱飞的
I'd know not to fly over volcanoes.
瞧我这个大傻冒"
I'm a freaking idiot."
巨龙版的克里斯托弗·沃肯[美国演员]
The dragon's Christopher Walken!
太了不起了
That's perfect.
艾米  该你了
All right, Amy, it's your turn.
我们还需要最后一击
We need one more hit.
-把他了结  -好的
- Finish him off! - Here we go.
Fifteen?
攻击成功  巨龙倒在了地上
It's a hit. The dragon collapses to the ground!
等一下
Wait.
他说...
And says...
"妈妈
"Mother?
是你吗
Is that you?
你的小宝贝要回家了"
Your little boy is coming home."
我不确定你们会不会  我反正今晚
Oh, I don't know about you guys, but I have been through
今晚我是大喜大悲到精疲力竭了
the emotional wringer tonight.
我可能是药水喝多了
This may be the potion talking,
但你真是个厉害的地下城主
but you are one fine-ass dungeon master.
是吗  我们回家后
Oh, yeah? Well, when we get home,
我会你带"体验"另一种完全不同的冒险
I'm gonna take you on a whole different adventure.
沃罗威茨主持的另一探险  加我一个
Another quest by Wolowitz? Count me in.
谢尔顿  他们说的是上床
Sheldon, they're talking about sex.
那我不玩了
Oh, then I'm out.
我有个主意
Ooh! I have an idea.
反正这事最近也不会成真
Since it's not happening anytime soon,
不如你的角色和你的角色
why don't your character and your character
在游戏中来一炮
do it in the game?
来声援一下
Come on, back me up here.
我对谢尔顿和艾米施爱情咒
Okay, I cast a love spell on Sheldon and Amy.
不好意思  以为你们还会这样
Sorry, I thought you were gonna do that...
爱情咒起作用了
The love spell takes effect.
谢尔顿看向艾米时
When Sheldon looks at Amy,
发现她是他生平见过最美丽的半兽人
she is the most beautiful half-orc he's ever seen,
他心里阵阵欲望涌现
and he's overcome with a desire
只想扯开她的盔甲
to rip her armor off
温柔地凝视她那四个毛茸茸的咪咪
and gaze fondly at her four hairy breasts.
艾米眼中的谢尔顿  他看起来就像是
When Amy sees Sheldon, he looks...
谢尔顿这个样子  因为她就好这口
well, just like Sheldon, 'cause apparently she's into that.
你们会怎么做
What do you do?
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
就说让女人玩龙与地下城不好吧
You see what happens when you let girls play D & D?
艾米
Amy.
什么事
What?
我从来没敲过自己房间的门
I've never knocked on my own door before.
真够刺激的
That was a wild ride.
你不用进来安慰我
You don't have to come in here and cheer me up.
谢谢
Thank you.
你能出来告诉其他人吗
Would you go tell everyone else that?
因为他们可不是这么想
Because they sure think otherwise.
我告诉你他们是怎么想的
I'll tell you what they think.
他们觉得我们的恋爱关系是一个笑话
They think our relationship is a joke.
我不觉得我们的恋爱关系是一个笑话
Well, I don't think our relationship is a joke.
我觉得
I think
"一匹马走进酒吧
"A horse goes into a bar,
酒保说  为什么拉长一张马脸[闷闷不乐]"
bartender says, 'Why the long face?'"
这种才是笑话
That's a joke.
还是个非常好笑的笑话  因为马的脸很长
It's a good one, too, because a horse has a long face.
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
我们到底会不会变成亲密的男女关系
are we ever going to have an intimate relationship?
天啊
Oh, my.
这个话题够尴尬的
That's an uncomfortable topic.
艾米
Amy...
我在认识你之前
before I met you,
我从未有兴趣跟任何人变得亲密
I never had any interest in being intimate with anyone.
现在呢
And now?
现在什么
And now what?
你现在有兴趣了吗
Do you have any interest now?
并不排除这种可能性
I have not ruled it out.
对我开黄腔呢
Talk dirty to me.
我知道你可能不这样想  但是
I know it doesn't seem like it to you, but,
对我来说  我们的关系
for me, what we have
已经是极度亲密了
is extremely intimate.
我想我知道
I guess I know that.
只是
It's just...
我的内心想要更多
part of me wants more.
更多
More?
瞧瞧咱们
I mean, look at us.
才三年时间  就已经在床上了
It's only been three years; here we are in bed together.
走吧
Come on.
我们出去吧
Let's go back out there.
不  等等
Y... Well, no. Hold on.
我的精灵魔法师和你的半兽人战士
My elven magic-user and your half-orc warrior
的确是被施了爱情咒
did have a love spell cast on them.
如果不继续玩下去
We wouldn't really be playing the game right
就是没遵守游戏规则
if we didn't see that through.
好吧
Okay.
我们刚刚杀了一条龙
I believe that, uh, we just killed a dragon.
其他人在捡尸体上的宝物时
While the others pillage the corpse,
我将你带到一个隐蔽的区域
I lead you to a secluded area
在那里  我想脱掉你的皮革盔甲
where I attempt to remove your leather armor.
脱掉了
It comes off.
你怎么做
What do you do?
我
I...
吻上你的嘴唇
...kiss you... on the lips.
我回吻你的...
I kiss you back on the...
嘴唇
...lips as well.
到你了
Your turn.
我脱掉了你的盔甲
I... remove your armor.
你会怎么做
What do you do?
我饥渴地爱抚你的
I... erotically caress your...
-鼻子  -继续扔
- ...nose. - Keep rolling.
你们已经在里面好一会儿了
Hey, you guys have been in there for a while.
-还好吗  -挺好的  多谢
- You doing okay? - We're fine, thank you.
我们只想说  我们非常抱歉刚才
Okay, we just want to say, we feel really bad about...
走开  谢尔顿正准备轻咬我的...
Go away! Sheldon is nibbling on my...
14  太棒了
14! Yes!